Hello friends, ICIC LBRD company has
announced for its shareholders yesterday.  The
company has also given a dividend notice letter
to BS and NSC exchanges.
In this letter, the company has clearly stated
that it is going to give its shareholders a
final dividend of ₹7 per equity share
and the record date fixed by the company for this dividend is
June 6, 2025.  On
June 6, 2025, anyone who has
this share of ICICI LBRD company in their demat account will become
eligible here.
For this dividend amount of ₹7 per share.  Also, let us
tell you that if you
want to get dividend in this company, then
you will have to buy this share before June 5.  Only then, on the
record date, this share will
come into your demat account and you will be eligible
for this dividend amount.  Along with this, let us
tell you that even if you sell the shares of this company on the record
date, which is on 6th June,
you will still be eligible here and
you will still get this dividend amount.  Also, let us
tell you that the company will credit
this dividend amount in the bank accounts of eligible shareholders
before 7 July 2025.  So friends, a big
update is coming out here for the shareholders of ICICI LBRD company.   If you are
new to my channel then please subscribe to the channel.
Dividend
related videos will continue to come in future also.  Thank you.